让我们来谈谈有关权限的问题  当每个应用程序的APK已经安装的时候
Let's talk about permissions, when each app APK is installed,
它被给予了它自己的特有的Linux用户ID
it's given it's own unique Linux user ID. And each
并且每个应用都在Android虚拟机内运行在自己的实例中
app runs within its instance in the Android Virtual machine.
由于每个应用程序时完全在沙箱中运行的
[SOUND] As a result each app is completely sand boxed.
它的文件处理和其他的资源是其他应用程序不能访问的
Its files processes and other resources are inaccessible
这个沙箱的运作方法确保了在默认情况下
to other apps. This sandboxing approach is used to
没有任何应用程序可以访问到敏感的数据
ensure that by default no app can access sensitive
或执行操作并且可能对其他的应用程序  系统  或用户
data or perform actions that could adversely impact other
产生不利的影响  比如说像访问互联网
apps, the OS, or users. Things like accessing the
获取用户的地理位置  或阅读或修改联系人的数据库
internet, getting the user's location, or reading or modifying
而不是让用户看到当你的应用
the contacts database. Rather than asking the user each
试图去访问某些敏感的内容时
time an app tries to access something sensitive you
所有需要请求的权限都显示出来
declared permissions that your app requires in it's manifest.
那样用会得到一列表的权限请求
You can get a list of all of the permission
你的应用程序所需的权限可以列在Android开发者站点上
your app may require here at the Android developer site.
所以  为什么不请求所有的权限而再也不用担心权限问题呢
So, why not just ask for all the permissions and
是的  当用户安装你的应用程序时
never worry about it again? Well, when users install
随着更人性化的描述
your app their greeted with this dialogue which lists all
在这个对话框中列出所有你需要的请求的权限
of the permissions that you've requested along with the more
没有说这个应用程序就是为了想偷取我数据
user-friendly descriptions. Nothing says this app was built by hackers
抢劫我房子  清空我账户并且
who want to steal my data, rob my house, clear out my
拍摄和分享我的裸露的照片
bank account, and take and share nude pictures of me like
做出一个伪天气应用想要访问我的设备上的所有权限的黑客
a weather app that wants access to every permission on the
最好的做法是请求绝对最低权限
device. Best practice is to request the absolute minimum of permissions.
每次你需要请求一个新的权限
Every time you need to request a new permission, take it
把它标注上并且思考是否有其他的选择
as a flag to stop and consider if there are other
可以达到同样的目的  例如
alternatives that might achieve the same goal. For example, using an
去直接使用相机的应用程序而不是直接访问摄像头
intent to launch the camera app, rather than accessing the camera, directly.
之后我们会看一些与其他应用程序共享数据的方式
Later, we'll look at ways to share your data with
使你想请求的和内容提供的去创建应用程序沙箱之间的桥梁
other apps, using intents and content providers to create bridges
你可以在这些实例中
between these apps sandboxs. You can declare and use those
声明和使用这些权限
permissions in these instances to
去限制和访问用户的敏感信息
similarly restrict access to sensitive information.